Zack, Arnold M. Additional Arbitration Files 5861
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files
1986-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold M.
5861
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records.
3126531
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 19, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 16, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Zack, Arnold.
3126531
- American Museum of Natural History - Lorusso Corp.. (Box 1)
  - American Museum of Natural History - AFSCME (4/25/88), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ansonia Board of Education (3/4/88), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bailey Corporation - Hampton, NH (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Boston Edison (9/20/88), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Boston Edison/Local 387 (10/31/88), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Boston Ed. - Braintree, MA (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Boston School Comm. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Boston Edison/Local 369 - Braintree, MA (11/7/88), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Boston Edison/Local 369 - Braintree, MA (12/12/88), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Boston Edison/Local 369 - Braintree, MA (12/15/88), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Brown University - Local 134 (5/2/88), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cambridge School Comm. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Charles River Consulting (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Conway School Board (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Crown, Cork, and Seal - Boston, MA (7/21/88), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Diamond Fibre Production Inc. - Springfield, MA (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Firefighters #1312 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Exon Seamen's Union - Elizabeth, NJ (6/13/88), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - PLB 4514 CFLA No. 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - PLB 4514 CFLA No. 2 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - PLB 4514 CFLA No. 3 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - PLB 4515 CFLA No. 4 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - PLB 4514 CFLA No. 5 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - PLB 4514 CFLA No. 6 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - PLB 4514 CFLA No. 7 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - FLA East Coast Railway (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Greyhound Hotel and Rest Workers Local 118 - Akron, Ohio (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - ITT World Communications - Communications Workers of America (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - James River Corp. - Bangor, ME (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - James River Corp. - Bangor, ME (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Jorgensen Steel Co. - Philadelphia, PA (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Keene Police Patrol - Keene, NH (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Lamoille Valley RR - Public Law Board No. 2252 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Legal Aid Society - New York, NY (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - City of Lewiston Local 785 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Litchfield Factfinding (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Maine State Troopers Association (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Alperin/Eastern Smelting - National Railway Passenger Corp.. (Box 2)
  - Alperin/Eastern Smelting (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bay State Bus/ATU - 5/22 AAA Boston (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - PLB 4598 (3/10/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Belt Railway Co. of Chicago (3/3/88), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bethlehem (NH) School Board - Bethlehem Teachers Association (4/12/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Boston Edison/UWUA (4/7/89) - Braintree, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Boston Edison/UWUA Local 369 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Boston Edison/UWUA 387 AAA Boston (Cancelled 4/4) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bow School District NEA Meditation (2/10/88), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Brookline/Brookline Police Association (8/30/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Caesars Boardwalk Regency Hotel Casino - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees - Atlantic City, NJ (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chicago and Northwestern/UTU (5/31/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Coca Cola/Teamsters - Auburn, MA (1/11/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Fraser Paper LTD/UPIU (10/25/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - George A. Fuller Co. - Thames Valley Steel - Boston (2/2/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - GG Distributors/Teamsters - North Haven, CT (9/13/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Gardner Police/Gardner City Hall (9/12/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - General Ship/J. Sanchez - Suffolk Superior Court (1/12/90), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Giradi Distributors Inc/Truck Drivers (3/17/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Gloucester Engineering Local 38 - Rockport, MA (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Harris, Kendall & Titlebaum Mass Mediation Service (3/14/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Hercules Incorporated - Oil, Chemical, Atomic Works (5/28/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Goffstown School Board - Goffstown, NH (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - James River - Bangor, ME (10/17) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Kollmorgen IAMAW (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - State of Maine AFSCME - Augusta, ME (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Manchester Professional Firefighters (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Massachusetts Teachers Association (5/23/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - MTA/Agency Fee Challengers (11/15/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Mt. Anthony, VT (11/20/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Nat RR Passenger Corp. - Philadelphia, PA (1/27/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - National RR Passenger Corporation - Philadelphia, PA (3/22/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - National Railroad Passenger Corporation (5/17/89), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Maine Cnetral RR - Public Law Bd. 4396. (Box 3)
  - Maine Central RR/UTU Public Law Board 4068 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - MBTA/RLEA - Boston (6/28-30/88), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mass Mediation - Boston (12/21/87), 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Teachers Association - Field Services Org. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Nashua School Board/Teachers Union - Nashua, NH (10/31/88), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Naval Shipyard - Portsmouth, NH (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Department of the Navy - Portsmouth, NH (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - New Fairfield Board of Education (1/25/88), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - New Hampshire School Boards Association Workshop - Merrimack, NH (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Newington Mediation/Fact Finding (6/21/88), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Newport School Board/Teacher Association (9/16/88), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Opera Co. of Boston/American Guild of Musical Artists (12/16/86), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Newington School Board (1988) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - PA Power and Lighting Local 1600 - Allentown, PA (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Public Law Board 2545 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - PLB 4068 Case 6 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - PLB 4068 Case 7 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - PLB 4068 Case 8 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - PLB 4068 Case 9 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - PLB 4068 Case 10 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - PLB 4068 Case 11 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - PLB 4068 Case 12 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - PLB 4068 Case 13 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - PLB 4068 Case 14 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - PLB 4068 Case 15 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - PLB 4068 Case 16 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - PLB 4068 Case 17 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - PLB 4068 Case 18 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - PLB 4068 Case 19 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - PLB 4068 Case 20 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - PLB 4068 Case 22 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - PLB 4068 Case 23 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - PLB 4068 Case 24 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - PLB 4068 Case 25 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - PLB 4068 Case 26 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - PLB 4068 Case 27 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - PLB 4068 Case 28 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - PLB 4068 Case 29 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - PLB 4068 Case 30 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - PLB 4068 Case 31 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - PLB 4068 Case 32 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - PLB 4068 Case 33 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - PLB 4068 Case 34 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - PLB 4068 Case 35 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - PLB 4068 Case 36 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - PLB 4068 Case 37 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - PLB 4068 Case 38 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - PLB 4068 Case 39 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - PLB 4068 Case 40 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - PLB 4068 Case 41 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - PLB 4068 Case 42 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - PLB 4068 Case 43 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - PLB 4068 Case 44 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - PLB 4068 Case 45 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - PLB 4068 Case 46 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - PLB 4068 Case 21 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - PLB 4068 Case 47 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - PLB 4068 Case 48 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - PLB 4068 Case 49 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - PLB 4068 Case 50 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - PLB 4068 Case 51 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - PLB 4068 Case 52 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - PLB 4068 Case 53 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - PLB 4068 Case 54 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - PLB 4068 Case 755 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - PLB 4068 Case 56 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - PLB 4068 Case 57 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - PLB 4068 Case 58 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - PLB 4068 Case 59 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - PLB 4068 Case 60 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - PLB 4396 Delaware and Hudson/TCU (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority. (Box 4)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 3) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 4) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 5) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 6) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 7) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 8) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 9) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 10) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 11) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 12) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 13) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 14) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 15) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 16) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 17) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 18) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 19) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 20) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 21) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 22) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority and Local 589: Interest Arbitration Vol. 1 (Day 23) (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority. (Box 5)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority v. Local 589 - Vol. 24 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority v. Local 589 - Vol. 25 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority v. Local 589 - Vol. 26 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority v. Local 589 - Vol. 27 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority v. Local 589 - Vol. 28 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority v. Local 589 - Vol. 29 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority v. Local 589 - Vol. 30 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority v. Local 589 - Vol. 31 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Memorandums of Understanding (16A-M) and Award of Arbitrator (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority - Affirmative Action Plan (1/1/88 - 1/1/94) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Introduction UX1 and Wage Maintenance UX5 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Life Insurance, Instructional Allowance, Written Reports, and Vacation (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Union Exhibits 82-107 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Union Exhibits 108-133 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Union Exhibits 135 - 171 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Union Exhibits 172-214 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Union Exhibits 215-240 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Union Exhibits 241-285 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Union Exhibits 286-308 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Union Exhibits 309-335 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Union Exhibits 336-346 and Agreement with Massachusetts and AFL-CIO (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority. (Box 6)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transport Authority v. Local 589: Opinion and Award and Memorandums of Understanding (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Local 589 v. Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority: Brief on Behalf of Union (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 2-17 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 18-61 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 62-103 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 104-152 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 153-184 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 184-245 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 246-293 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 294-299 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 301-334 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 335-377 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 378-393 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Exhibits 394-407 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 15)
- New Hampshire Employees Assn. - USPS. (Box 7)
  - New Hampshire Employees Association - State of New Hampshire (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Newport School Comm/RI AFSCME (5/18/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - NIDEC-Torin/UAW - Torrington, CT (10/27/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - PA Power and Light Co. - Allentown, PA (2/1/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - PA Power and Lighting Co. - Allentown, PA (4/10/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Mass Mediation Service - Boston (3/2/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Polysar Inc/IEU - Chicopee, MA (7/13/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Polysar/ICWU - Leominster (11/2/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Portsmouth School Board (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Princeton Packaging - Hazelton, PA (7/12/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Procter and Gamble - Elizabeth, NJ (4/11/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Board and Association Contract (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Procter and Gamble - Newark Airport (4/26/88), 1988 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Pueblo Education Association School District No. 60 (5/19/88) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Pueblo Education Association - Pueblo, CO (9/27/89), 1988 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Rite Aid/RWDSU - Charleston, WV (5/1/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Rochester Federation of Teachers - Rochester, NH (1/13/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Rochester Telephone Corporation/Local 1170 (7/11/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - St. Vrain, Colorado (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Sanford Police Association - R. Beaulieu (5/16/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Seehan/John Hancock - Mass. Mediation (8/23/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Sheraton Boston (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Sinai Hospital/District 1199 - Baltimore, MD (2/6/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - TWA/Pilot System Board of Adjustment - New York, NY (2/14/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - TWA Systems Board/ALPA (9/12-13/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Triborough Bridge and Tunnel (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Trump Plaza/Hotel - Atlantic City (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - UNISYS/IUE - Great Neck, NY (9/15/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - USPS/National Rural Letter Carriers (1/12/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - No Bill Settled Time (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Springfield, MA (1/23/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - USPS/APWU - Portland, ME (1/24/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - USPS/NALC - Syracuse, NY (1/30/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - USPS?APWU - Essex Junction, VT (1/31/89), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Scott Paper Co. - USPS. (Box 8)
  - Scott Paper Co./United Paperworks Local 448 - Philadelphia, PA (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Shrewsbury Education Association - Shrewsbury, MA (12/23/88), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Springfield Terminal Railway (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - TWA System Board of Adjustment - JFK Marriott (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - TWA System Board of Adjustment - JFK Marriott (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - TWA Pilot System Boards of Adjustment - New York, NY (4/5/88), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - TWA Pilot System Boards of Adjustment - New York, NY (5/26/88), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - TWA - Kansas City, MO (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - TWA - Kansas City (7/19/88) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - TWA Kansas City, MO (6/16/88), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - TWA Pilot System Board of Adjustment - New York, NY (8/2/88), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - TWA Pilot System Board of Adjustment - New York, NY (8/3/88), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - TW St. Louis, MO (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - TWA Kansas City (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - TWA _ Bryant Grievant - JFK Airport (11/2/88), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - TWA St. Louis, MO (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - TWA Pilot System Board of Adjustment - New York, NY (6/7/88), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - TWA Pilot System Board of Adjustment - New York, NY (12/14/88), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - TWA - St. Louis, MO (12/16/88), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - TWA Pilot System Board of Adjustment - New York, NY (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Boston, MA (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Jersey City, NJ (11/17/87), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - New York, NY (1/12/88), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - USPS/APWU - Hartford, CT (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - USPS/APWU - Jersey City, NJ (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - USPS/APWU - New York, NY (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Kearny, NJ (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - USPS/APWU - New York, NY (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - USPS/NAMH - Kearny, NJ (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - USPS/NAHM - Albany, NY (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - USPS - New York, NY (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - USPS - New Hampshire (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - PLB 4398 - Boston and Maine (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - USPS - New York, NY (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - USPS - Providence, RI (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - USPS - New York, NY (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - USPS - Stamford, CT (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - USPS - Springfield (Box 8, Folder 38)
- USPS. (Box 9)
  - USPS Springfield (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - USPS - Springfield, MA (4/19/88) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - USPS - Hackensack, NJ (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - USPS - Terry (4/28/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - USPS - Stamford (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Springfield, MA (4/29/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - USPS - Springfield (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Kearny, NJ (5/3/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Mailhandlers - New York, NY (5/4/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Mailhandlers - St. Louis, MO (5/4/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - New York, NY (5/4/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Kearny, NJ (5/5/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Jersey City, NJ (5/6/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Jersey City, NJ (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - USPS - Hudson, NY (5/10/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - USPS Mailhandlers - New York, NY (5/24/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - USPS - Newark, NJ (5/25/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - USPS - Boston, MA (6/6/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - USPS - Boston, MA (6/6/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Jersey City, NJ (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Jersey City, NJ (6/8/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Kearny, NJ (7/11/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Buffalo, NY (7/12/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Garden City, NY (7/13/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - New York, NY (7/14/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Wappingers, NY (8/8/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Kearny, NJ (8/9/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - USPS/NALC - Brockton, MA (9/6/88), 1988 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- USPS. (Box 10)
  - USPS - Willimantic, CT (9/7/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - USPS - Edison, NJ: Kotter (1 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - USPS - Pittel (2 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - USPS - Kotter (3 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - USPS - Sexton (4 of 4) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - New York, NY (6/10/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - USPS - Lynn, MA (7/27/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - New Haven, CT (8/10/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Boston (9/13/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Warwick, RI (9/14/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - USPS - Springfield, MA (9/15/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - USPS - Hartford, CT (9/22/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - USPS - Southbridge, MA (10/12/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Boston, MA (11/1/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - USPS - Providence, RI (11/3/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - USPS - Plattsburgh, NY (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Springfield, MA (11/23/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - New Haven, CT (12/2/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Portland, ME (12/5/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - USPS/Mailhandlers - Springfield, MA (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Waltham School Department - Waltham, MA (10/14/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Windham Factfinding (1/22/88), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Yale University and Federation of Union Employees (1971) (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - USPS - New York, NY (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - USPS - New York, NY (10/2/89), 1989 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - USPS - Springfield (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - USPS - Wappingers Falls (10/4/89), 1989 (Box 10, Folder 27)